A Finding Aid to the Jackson Pollock and Lee Krasner Papers, circa 1914-1984, bulk 1942-1984, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Lee Krasner Papers, circa 1927-1984; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 8.6 Linear feet Box 7-15, 17
  - Biographical Material, circa 1927-1983; 2.1; Archival Resource Key
    - Award Certificates, 1972-1982; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in Box 17, F1) (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Address Books, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - "Personal Mementos from England Trip", 1965; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 7, Folder 21-22)
    - Award Certificates, 1982; Archival Resource Key; (Scanned with Box 9, F19) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, circa 1941-1984; 2.2; Archival Resource Key
    Lee Krasner's correspondence spans over forty years, but the bulk of it ranges from 1970 to her death in 1984. Found here is correspondence with galleries and gallery owners that represented her, exhibited her work, or requested her work for potential exhibitions. Krasner was friends with many artists and art professionals and her personal correspondence includes many letters from artists such as Philip Johnson, Ray Eames, Cleve Gray, and Hans Namuth. She also corresponded with art historians and critics, curators, collectors, arts and social organizations, admirers, and family members. Additionally, this series includes fan mail, student inquiries, correspondence with journalists and publishers, requests for her to lecture, and business correspondence on the sale of her work. There are numerous letters and telegrams congratulating Krasner on exhibitions, such as the 1965 Whitechapel retrospective and extensive documentation of her 1958 commission to create a mural for Uris Brothers, Inc.
    See Index for List of Notable Correspondents from Series 2.2
    Letters are arranged chronologically and include both letters received by Krasner and handwritten or typed drafts sent by Krasner. Later in her life many of the drafts were written by her secretary.
    Index: List of Notable Correspondents from Series 2.2
    List represents only a selection of correspondents.
    Albright-Knox Art Gallery
    American Federation of Arts
    Appelhof, Ruth Ann
    Asher, Elise
    Australian National Gallery
    Barron, Maida
    Berkson, Bill
    Collier, Oscar
    Cooper Union
    County of Nassau Office of Cultural Development
    Diamonstein, Barbaralee
    Dickler, Gerald
    Eames, Ray
    Englesmith, Tejas
    Erskine, Halley
    Forge, Andrew (Yale University)
    Franklin Siden Gallery
    Friedman, B. H.
    Friedman, Sanford
    Glaser, Bruce
    Goodman, Naomi
    Gray, Cleve
    Gregory-Hood, Alex (Rowan Gallery)
    Guggenheim Museum
    Guild Hall
    Holladay, Billie
    Howard, Richard
    Howell, Douglas Morse
    Hubbard, E. W.
    Janie C. Lee Gallery
    Johnson, Philip
    Landau, Ellen
    Lauck, Anthony
    Lloyd, Frank
    Marlborogh Fine Art, Ltd.
    Martha Jackson Gallery
    Matter, Mercedes
    McHenry, Barnabas (Barney)
    Michael, Marjorie
    Museum of Modern Art
    Myers, John Bernard
    Namuth, Hans
    Nemser, Cindy
    New York WPA Artists, Inc.
    Nochlin, Linda
    Novak, Barbara
    O'Connor, Francis
    Oppler, Ellen
    Ossorio, Alfonso
    Pace Gallery
    Parrish Art Museum
    Pavia, Philip
    Pollock, Jay
    Rago, Louise Elliott
    Robert Miller Gallery
    Robertson, Bryan
    Rose, Barbara
    Russell, Bertrand
    Schilling, Marge
    School of Visual Arts
    Sidney Janis Gallery
    Siegel, Adele
    Smithsonian Institution
    Spaeth, Elaine
    Stasik, Andrew
    Still, Clyfford
    Stony Brook Foundation
    Tate Gallery
    Thaw, Eugene V.
    Thayer, Jeanne
    Valliere, James
    Van Fossen, Ted
    Whitechapel Art Gallery
    Whitney, David
    Whitney Museum of American Art
    Wise, Howard
    - Correspondence, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1960; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 8, Folder 3-6)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1965; Archival Resource Key; (9 folders) (Box 8, Folder 7-15)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1970; Archival Resource Key; (7 folders) (Box 8, Folder 16-22)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1976; Archival Resource Key; (19 folders) (Box 8, Folder 23-41)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1980; Archival Resource Key; (21 folders) (Box 9, Folder 1-21)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1984; Archival Resource Key; (20 folders) (Box 9, Folder 22-41)
  - Interview Transcripts, circa 1965-1979; 2.3; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries contains transcripts of interviews of Lee Krasner conducted by various art historians and journalists. The interviews discuss Krasner's work, the early abstract expressionist movement, her relationship with Jackson Pollock, and the "New York art world". Two of the transcripts are for broadcast interviews, including a 1979 interview with Barbara Novak for WGBH New Television Workshop, Boston. Transcripts are arranged chronologically. Audio recordings for these interviews are filed in Series 2.10.
    - Bruce Glaser Interview, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Barbara Cavaliere Interview, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Andrew Forge Interview, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Emily Wasserman Interview, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Barbara Rose Interview, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Gaby Rogers Interview, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Barbaralee Diamonstein Interview, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Barbara Rose Interview, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Helen Weinberg Interview, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Richard Howard Interview, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Ellen G. Landau Interview, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Barbara Novak Interview, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Writings by Others, circa 1965-1981; 2.4; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries includes draft essays, many with annotations, about Lee Krasner and her artwork. Items are arranged chronologically.
    - Ellen G. Landau, untitled manuscript, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - B. H. Friedman, "Lee Krasner,", 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Eleanor Munro, untitled manuscript, circa 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Deborah Daw, "Lee Krasner: On Climbing a Mountain of Porcelain", 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - John Myers, "An Imaginary Interview with Lee Krasner", 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Writings by Lee Krasner, circa 1977-1979; 2.5; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries includes a few lecture notes by Lee Krasner as well as handwritten notes about her life and memories.
    - Personal Notes and Lectures, 1977-1979, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Business and Financial Records, circa 1957-1983; 2.6; Archival Resource Key
    Scattered business and financial records date primarily from 1967 to 1983 and include exhibition checklists, conservation forms, loan forms, sales and price lists, warehouse and shipping receipts, guest lists, account statements and other handwritten lists and notes. There is documentation from the Robert Miller Gallery, Pace Gallery, the Whitney museum, and the Marlborough gallery.
    - Miscellaneous Business Records, 1957-1983, undated; Archival Resource Key; (9 folders) (Box 10, Folder 12-20)
    - Sales and Accounting Statements for Robert Miller Gallery, 1981-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Loan Forms and Checklists from "Lee Krasner Retrospective", 1983; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 22-23)
    - Financial Records, 1967-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Inventories, Marlborough Gallery, 1975-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Inventories, Pace Gallery, 1975-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Inventories, Robert Miller Gallery, 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Price Lists, 1972, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Mailing Lists, Marlborough Gallery, 1968, 1973; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 29-30)
    - Mailing Lists, Whitney Museum, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Mailing Lists, Pace Gallery, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Mailing Lists, Whitney Museum, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Mailing Lists, Pace Gallery, 1979, 1981; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 10, Folder 34-35)
    - Mailing Lists, Robert Miller Gallery, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Guest Lists, Robert Miller Gallery, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Scrapbook, 1965; 2.7; Archival Resource Key
    This scrapbook documents a 1965 exhibition of Krasner's work at Whitechapel Gallery in London. The scrapbook was created by the President of Marlborough Gallery, Pierre Levai, and includes news clippings about the event and photographs of the exhibition installation.
    - Whitechapel Gallery Exhibition Scrapbook, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Printed Material, circa 1942-1984; 2.8; Archival Resource Key
    Printed material documents Lee Krasner's career and includes solo and group exhibition catalogs, announcements, press releases, and numerous newspaper and magazine clippings. There are also newsletters, event calendars, annual reports, and documentary film announcements for films about Krasner. Schedules, directories, instructions, and other faculty materials are from Krasner's semester as a faculty member at Cooper Union. Miscellaneous printed material includes primarily programs, brochures, and invitations to events. There is also an "Odds and Ends" folder. Items are arranged by type of material and chronologically within each folder.
    - Exhibition Catalogs, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1942-1963; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 10, Folder 40-42)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1964-1975; Archival Resource Key; (7 folders) (Box 11, Folder 1-7)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key; (10 folders) (Box 11, Folder 8-17)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1982-1984; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 12, Folder 1-4)
    - Exhibition Announcements, 1949-1984, undated; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 12, Folder 5-8)
    - Press Releases, 1958-1983, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Material, 1968-1983, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 10-11)
    - Documentary Film Announcements, 1972-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Essay, "Jackson Pollock Works on Paper", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Reproductions of Artwork, circa 1981-1982, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Essay, "The American Abstract Expressionist Collection of the Sarah Campbell Blaffer Foundation", undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Newsletters, Events Calendars, and Annual Reports, 1960-1984, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 12, Folder 16-17)
    - Selected Chronology, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Exhibition info for "Lee Krasner at Martha Jackson", 1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Faculty Materials, The Cooper Union, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - The Subject of the Artist, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Exhibition Materials for "Krasner/Pollock: A Working Relationship", 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - 25 Artists, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - "Odds & Ends", 1969-1970, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - New Clippings, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - News Clippings, 1948-1974; Archival Resource Key; (5 folders) (Box 12, Folder 26-30)
    - News Clippings, 1975-1979; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 12, Folder 31-34)
    - News Clippings, 1981-1984; Archival Resource Key; (6 folders) (Box 13, Folder 1-6)
    - Magazine Clippings, 1952-1984, undated; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 13, Folder 7-9)
    - Photographs of Artists in Harper's Bazaar (Reproductions), 1951; Archival Resource Key; (Not scanned) (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Exhibition Poster, 1969; Archival Resource Key; (Not scanned) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, circa 1929-1983; 2.9; Archival Resource Key
    Lee Krasner's personal photographs and photographs of her artwork are filed here, including one of her painting in the studio and portraits of her at the WPA pier. The majority of the photographs in this subseries are professional portraits taken of Lee Krasner throughout her career. Some of the portraits depict her home and painting in her studio. Photographers of note are Hans Namuth, Renate Ponsold, and Ray Eames, and one by Irving Penn. All portraits of Krasner are grouped by photographer and arranged chronologically.
    Personal and family photographs include photos of Krasner on the beach, circa 1939, and with family and friends. Photographs of Krasner with Jackson Pollock were taken at the beach, with family, and at their home in the Springs. There are also photographs of the two of them outside of their home and in the studio, taken by Wilfred Zogbaum. There are photographs of Lee Krasner at various exhibitions, including her 1973 exhibition at the Whitney Museum of American Art.
    Photographs of artwork include photographs of Krasner's work in various medium, such as ink, collage, lithographs, and mosaic, as well as the artwork she did for the WPA. Photographs of artwork have not been scanned.
    - Personal Photographs, 1938-1982, undated; 2.9.1; Archival Resource Key
      - Early Portraits of Lee Krasner, 1938-1940, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Lee Krasner at the WPA Pier, circa 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Lee Krasner Personal and Family Photographs, circa 1939-1964, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 13-14)
      - Lee Krasner and Jackson Pollock, circa 1950, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 15-16)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Maurice Berezov, circa 1942, 1956, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Hans Namuth, 1955, 1958, undated; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in Box 17, F2) (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Halley Erskine, 1959; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in Box 17, F3) (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Paul De Vries, circa 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Paul De Vries, circa 1960-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Hans Namuth, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Ray Eames, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Bryan Wharton, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Bob Miller, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Mark Patiky, 1970; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in Box 17, F4) (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Portraits of Krasner by John Reed, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Irving Penn, 1972; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in Box 17, F5) (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Iris Schneider, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Portraits of Krasner by David Gahr, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Ann Chwatsky, circa 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Marjorie Michael, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Ray Eames, 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Lenore Seroka, circa 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Renate Ponsold, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Jesse Fernandez, circa 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Ernst Hans, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Waintrob-Budd, 1981; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in Box 17, F6) (Box 13, Folder 38)
      - Portraits of Krasner, Miscellaneous, 1950-1982, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders; Oversized items in Box 17, F7) (Box 13, Folder 39-40)
      - Lee Krasner's Home by Ray Eames, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 41)
      - Lee Krasner's Home by Jesse Fernandez, 1973, 1979, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 42-43)
      - Exhibition, University of Alabama, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 44)
      - Exhibition, Whitney Museum, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 45)
      - Exhibition, Brandeis University, 1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 46)
      - Exhibition, "Around Jackson Pollock: East Hampton, the 1950s", 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 47)
      - Exhibition, Centre Georges Pompidou, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 48)
      - Exhibitions, Miscellaneous, 1974, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 49)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Hans Namuth, 1955, 1958, undated; Archival Resource Key; (Scanned with Box 13, F18) (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Halley Erskine, 1959; Archival Resource Key; (Scanned with Box 13, F19) (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Mark Patiky, 1970; Archival Resource Key; (Scanned with Box 13, F26) (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Irving Penn, 1972; Archival Resource Key; (Scanned with Box 13, F28) (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Portraits of Krasner by Waintrob-Budd, 1981; Archival Resource Key; (Scanned with Box 13, F38) (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Portraits of Krasner, Miscellaneous, 1950-1982, undated; Archival Resource Key; (Scanned with Box 13, F39-40) (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Photographs of Artwork, 1929-1983, undated; 2.9.2; Archival Resource Key; (not scanned)
      - Charcoal Drawings, 1937-1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 50)
      - Oil on Paper, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 51)
      - Early Abstractions, 1938-1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 52)
      - Artwork for the WPA, circa 1940-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 13, Folder 53)
      - Little Image Paintings, 1946-1950; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
      - Ink Paintings, 1950-1958; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Paintings, 1942-1965, undated; Archival Resource Key; (8 folders; Oversized items in Box 17, F8) (Box 14, Folder 4-11)
      - Mosaic Table, 1947; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in Box 17, F9) (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Studies for Mosaic Project, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Collages, 1953-1979; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 14, Folder 14-16)
      - Lithographs, 1962-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous Artwork by Lee Krasner, 1929-1935, undated; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 18-19)
      - Unidentified Artwork, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Stable Gallery Collage Exhibition, 1955; Archival Resource Key; (Oversized items in Box 17, F10) (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Howard Wise Gallery Exhibition, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Marlborough Gallery Exhibition, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Marlborough Gallery Exhibition, 1969; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 24-25)
      - University of Alabama Exhibtion, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Reese Palley Gallery Exhibition, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Marlborough Gallery Exhibition, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Whitney Museum Exhibition, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Janie C. Lee Gallery Exhibition, 1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Pace Gallery Exhibition, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Janie C. Lee Gallery Exhibition, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - Nassau County Museum of Art Exhibition, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - Grey Art Gallery Exhibition, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 34)
      - Guild Hall Exhibition, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - Pace Gallery Exhibition, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 36)
      - Tate Gallery Exhibition, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 37)
      - Unidentified Exhibitions, 1954-1959, 1976, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 38)
      - Drawing by Tony Smith, 1945-1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 39)
      - Miscellaneous Proof Sheets, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 40)
      - Negatives, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 14, Folder 41)
      - Color Transparencies, 1938-1972, undated; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 15, Folder 1-3)
      - Paintings, 1942-1962, undated; Archival Resource Key; (See also Box 14, F4-11) (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Mosaic Table, 1947; Archival Resource Key; (See also Box 14, F12) (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Stable Gallery Collage Exhibition, 1955; Archival Resource Key; (See also Box 14, F21) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Audio and Video Recordings, circa 1964-1983; 2.10; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries consists primarily of audio recordings of interviews with Lee Krasner that discuss her career, her relationship with Jackson Pollock, and Pollock's career. The recordings include interviews conducted by John Gruen for the Casper Citron radio show, one for the Martha Dean radio show, and one for the "Today Show". Another interview of note was conducted by fellow artist Mercedes Matter. Transcripts for most of these interviews are filed in Series 2.3.
    Also found in this series are two recorded lectures given by Lee Krasner, and two copies VHS video recordings about Pollock and a 1982 exhibition of his work, "Pollock a Beaubourg". Items are arranged chronologically.
    - Lee Krasner Lecture at Nassau County Museum of Art, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Bruce Glaser Interview of Lee Krasner, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes letter from Glaser and notes. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mercedes Matter Interview of Lee Krasner, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Original; 1 Sound discs (CD) Duplicate (Box 15, Folder 6)
      CD is access copy.
    - John Gruen Interview of Lee Krasner, 1964; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound discs (lacquer) Original; 1 Sound tape reel Duplicate; 2 Sound cassettes Duplicates (Box 15, Folder 7-9)
      Cassettes are access copies.
    - Martha Dean Radio Show Interview of Lee Krasner, 1968; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette Duplicate; 1 Sound tape reel Original (Box 15, Folder 10-11)
      Cassette is access copy.
    - Dolores Holmes Interview of Lee Krasner, 1971; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - NBC "Today Show" Interview of Lee Krasner, 1973; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 15, Folder 13)